Guide to the Michele Zackheim Papers MSS.108
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Einstein
  - Subseries A: Research
    - Bernstein, Jeremy, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Besso, Michele, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Bial Family, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bibliography, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Birth Certificates (unidentified), undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Book dealers, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bota, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Brandies University Library, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Brian, Denis, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bunge, G von-alcoholism pamphlet owned by Mileva Einstein-Maric, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Christie's, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Chronology Notes, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Danube, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Dissertation Abstracts, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - DNA, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Dokmanovic, Slavica, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Dokmanivic family postcards, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Einstein, Albert-Albert Einstein: The Human Side, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Einstein, Albert, Archive at Hebrew University, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Einstein, Albert-Collected Papers v.1, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Einstein, Albert, divorce papers, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Einstein Albert, general, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Einstein, Albert, letters, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Einstein, Albert letters to and from Janos Plesch, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Einstein, Albert, marriage papers, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Einstein, Albert, news clippings, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Einstein, Albert, news clippings: Vreme, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Einstein, Albert, Passport and naturalization papers (photocopies), undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Einstein, Alfred, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Einstein, Eduard, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Einstein, Ethel, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Einstein, Evelyn, Adoption, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Einstein, Evelyn, general, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Einstein, Evelyn, interview, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Einstein, Evelyn, Novi Sad, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Einstein, Evelyn, Will, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Einstein, Hans Albert, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva-Bota/Stefanovic Correspondence, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, Correspondence, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, friends, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, general, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, Music, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, Places of Residence, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, School Records, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Einstein-Maric, Mileva, Zurich, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Einstein Family, General, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Einstein's Daughter, reader's reports, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Elfenbein, Stefan, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Europe, Bathing Resorts, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Europe: Telegraphic Code, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Europe: Temperatures, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Europe: Trains, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - European Immigrants, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Family Trees, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Flckiger, Max, "Albert Einstein and Switzerland", undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Forel, August, Die Sexuelle Frage owned by Mileva Einstein-Maric, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Forel, August, undated; 31142040610654 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - France, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Gajin Family, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Galic Family, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Golubovic, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Grendelmeir, Marie, Interview, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Herschdoerfer Family, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Holton, Gerald "Of Love, Physics and Other Passions", undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Hungary, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Hungary, adoption, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Hungary, Budapest, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Hurwitz, Aldolf, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Infeld Family, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Journal/Notes, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Kahler, Erich, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Konenkova, Margarita, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Kosanin, Aldolfina, Notes, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Kosanovic, Dragana, Mileva Einstein-Maric, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Krusedol Monastery, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Kumanov, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Laue, Max von, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Leo Baeck Institute, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Library Book Requests, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Library Call Slips, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Library Search Requests (1/2), undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Library Search Requests (2/2), undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Link, Louis, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Lyons, Jacqui, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - McGrail, Anne, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Maric, Dragisa, Interview, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Maric, Lieserl, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Maric, Milica (Agripina), undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Maric, Milos, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Maric, Milos, II, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Maric, Zorka, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Maric Family, Books, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Maric Family, Dividends, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Maric Family, France, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Maric Family, Germany, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Maric Family, Lawsuit with Peasant, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Maric Symposium, Novi Sad, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Marianoff, Diana, "Einstein, An Intimate Study of a Great Man", undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Markovic, Laza, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Markstein, George, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Markstein, Greta, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Markstein, Leopold, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Markstein, Richard, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Markstein Family, Austria, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Markstein Family, Berlin, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Markstein Family, Chronology, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Markstein Family, Documents, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Markstein Family, Paris, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Markstein Family, U.S., undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Markstein Family, Letters, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Markstein, London News, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Markstein/Rkert, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Max Planck Institute, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Medical: Birthing, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Medical: Congenital Malformations, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Medical: Congenital Malformations in Hungary, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Medical: Downs Syndrome, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Medical: Memory, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Medical: Psychological Aspects of Congenital Malformations, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Medical: Various, undated; 31142040610662 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Medicus, Heinrich, "The Friendship Among Three Singular Men", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Meichle, Adolf, "Albert Einstein's Years in Berne", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Meiter, Lise, "A Passion for Science", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Michelmore, Peter, "Einstein Profile of the Man", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Moonies, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Music, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - National Archives, U.S., undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Nori Sad, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Nori Sad Newspapers, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Nori Sad, Postcards, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Notebook, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Notes, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Notes/Materials, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Nuffield College Library, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Orient Express, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Overbye, Dennis, "Einstein in Love", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Palmer, Lilli, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Petrovic, Jelena "Live Like a Refugee", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Physics, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Plesch, Diary, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Plesch, Janos and Peter, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Plesch, Janos, Party Book, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Plesch, John, "Janos, the Story of a Doctor", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Popovic, Milan, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Proverbs, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Pyenson, Lewis, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Pyenson, Lewis, "Einstein's Natural Daughter", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Pyenson, Lewis, "The Young Einstein", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Reiners, Ludwig, "The Lamps Went Out in Europe", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Romanov, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Rosendorf Family, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Russia, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Ruzic Interview, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Savic, Julka, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Savic, Zorka, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Savic Family, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Schulmann, Robert, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Seelig, Carl Albert Einstein: A Documentary Biography, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Serbia: Addresses, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Serbia: Almanacs and Calendars, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Serbia: Charms, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Serbia: Chronological History, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Serbia: Cultural Traditions, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Serbia: Customs, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Serbia: Fabric, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Serbia: First Trip Notes, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Serbia: Flowers, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Serbia: Food, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Serbia: General, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Serbia: Graves, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Serbia: Humor, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Serbia: Maps, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Serbia: Maps, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Serbia: News, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Serbia: Oral Tradition, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Serbia: Oral Women Poets, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Serbia: Proverbs, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Serbia: Songs and Poems, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Serbia: Women and Children, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Shearer, Rhonda Roland, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Slavic Transliteration, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Sonderegger, Eva Meili, Interview, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Stachel, John-"Albert Einstein and Mileva Maric", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Stachel, John-"Einstein and Ether Drift Experiments", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Stachel, John-"The Scientific Relationship of Albert Einstein and Mileva Maric", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Stachel, John, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Steamship Travel, Danube, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Stein, Lola, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Stoldolski, A., Internet Search, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Switzerland, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Time Zones, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Titel, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Travel, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Trbuhovic, Ljubomir, Interview, undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Trbuhovic-Gjuric, Desanka--"Im Schatten Albert Einsteins", undated; 31142040610670 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Troemel-Ploetz, Senta-"Mileva Einstein Maric", undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Troemel-Ploetz, Senta, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Twins, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Vienna, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Vienna News, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Vujicic, Stojan, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Weyl, Hermann, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - World War I, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Wortsman, Peter, "A Modern Way to Die", undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Yugoslavia: Adoption Search Requests, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Yugoslavia: Archives, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Yugoslavia: Belgrade, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Yugoslavia: General, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Yugoslavia: Visas, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Zackel, Ludek, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Zurich, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Research Binder #1 (1/2), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Research Binder #1 (2/2), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Research Binder #2 (1/2), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Research Binder #2 (2/2), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Research Binder #3, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Research Binder #5 (1/6), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Research Binder #5 (2/6), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Research Binder #5 (3/6), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Research Binder #5 (4/6), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Research Binder #5 (5/6), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Research Binder #5 (6/6), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Research Binder #6 (1/3), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Research Binder #6 (2/3), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Research Binder #6 (3/3), undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Research Binder #7, undated; 31142040610688 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Note Card File, undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Books, Photographs, and Notes, 1947-2005 (Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 22)
  - Subseries B: Manuscripts
    Comprises of drafts, proofs, and corrections to Einstein's Daughter. Arranged in a loose chronology of the drafts.
    - First Typescript (1/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - First Typescript (2/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - First Typescript (3/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - First Typescript (4/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - First Typescript (5/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - First Typescript (6/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - First Typescript (7/7), August 1, 1991, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Second Typescript (1/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Second Typescript (2/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Second Typescript (3/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Second Typescript (4/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Second Typescript (5/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Second Typescript (6/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Second Typescript (7/7), undated; 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Copyeditor's Notes, June 18, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - Copyedited Bibliography, June 21, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - First Proof w/corrections (1/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - First Proof w/corrections (2/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - First Proof w/corrections (3/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - First Proof w/corrections (4/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - First Proof w/corrections (5/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - First Proof w/corrections (6/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - First Proof w/corrections (7/7), July 19, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (1/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (2/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (3/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (4/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (5/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (6/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Second Proof w/corrections (7/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (1/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (2/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (3/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (4/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (5/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (6/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Second Proof w/ additional corrections (7/7), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Second Proof, designer's copy (1/6), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Second Proof, designer's copy (2/6), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Second Proof, designer's copy (3/6), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Second Proof, designer's copy (4/6), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Second Proof, designer's copy (5/6), July 23, 1999, 31142040610696 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Second Proof, designer's copy (6/6), July 23, 1999, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Corrections-Kathy Anderson, July 27, 1999, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Photo Proofs, August 11, 1999, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Photo Credits, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Inserts and Corrections, June 1, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Final Proof (1/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Final Proof (2/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Final Proof (3/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Final Proof (4/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Final Proof (5/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Final Proof (6/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Final Proof (7/7), August 17, 2000, 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Proofer's Corrections, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Copyedited Endnotes, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - Bibliography, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - Incomplete Corrected Typescript (1/2), undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Incomplete Corrected Typescript (2/2), undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - List of Illustrations / Plate Proofs, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - Partial Typescript, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Incomplete Manuscript, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Subseries C: Legal
    Contains copyright information, permissions to quote and release forms, arranged alphabetically by type of document.
    - Copyright Information, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Copyright Materials, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Copyright: Hebrew University, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Interview Releases, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - Letters of Confidentiality, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Permissions Form, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Permissions, Books, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Permissions, Forel, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Permissions, Photos, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Putnam Legal File, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Translator's Permission to reproduce, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Subseries D: Correspondence
    Correspondence to and from a broad range of sources, contacts and informants. Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - Adelson, Alan, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Albert Einstein Institute, Hebrew University, undated; 31142040610704 (Box 7, Folder 312)